{
    "id": "aaa5f6fbc15c4310931557285cbd9003",
    "title": "Grammar And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The weather was uncertain but we went swimming …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anyway",
                "anyhow",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e9190023af664e5da55add14794a40a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shy child sat …………………….. from the other children.",
            "description": "To sit apart is to sit by oneself.",
            "answers": [
                "apart",
                "off",
                "aside"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6faa04214b794829ae7d99b0eabb27de"
        },
        {
            "question": "Today’s students are not ………………………….. about religion.",
            "description": "Apathetic means unconcerned",
            "answers": [
                "pathetic",
                "apathetic",
                "empathetic"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff473e6f6cdd4e929606d935f3038a1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Public ………………………….. can lead to bad government.",
            "description": "Apathy means lack of interest.",
            "answers": [
                "apathy",
                "empathy",
                "sympathy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "730af9f1c1dd4c51a90bb79f6221c565"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is your ………………………… of the situation?",
            "description": "Appraisal means judgement.",
            "answers": [
                "appraisal",
                "apprisal"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "390205ecc9b7482d914e814fe2e2dedf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police expect to ………………………… the kidnappers before nightfall.",
            "description": "Apprehend means catch.",
            "answers": [
                "apprehend",
                "comprehend",
                "ascribe"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e681c1ddf29c4c4a8681afe024cf8b13"
        },
        {
            "question": "The prospect of major surgery would make anyone ………………………………",
            "description": "Apprehensive means anxious.",
            "answers": [
                "apprehensive",
                "comprehensive",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42ea2fae21014530a3cc13aaa6563a6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police should ……………………… an arrested person of his right to remain silent.",
            "description": "Apprise means inform or notify.",
            "answers": [
                "appraise",
                "apprise",
                "aprize"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5ef68791f714df5b042d6361706c601"
        },
        {
            "question": "No teacher can ………………………… cheating on exams.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "admit of",
                "approve of",
                "accept of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19eca42cb85f4d0e95960a9f696b8258"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was an …………………….. patriot.",
            "description": "Ardent means zealous.",
            "answers": [
                "ardous",
                "ardent",
                "arduous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a303b31853a64c4b82aad569f6c615f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Climbing the mountain was an ………………………… task.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arduous",
                "ardous",
                "ardent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e435b08b51174f2abe76f491a196e440"
        },
        {
            "question": "Accidents can ……………………….. from carelessness.",
            "description": "Arise can mean come into being or stem from. ",
            "answers": [
                "rise",
                "arise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9474573e81245ed8b63091d1567e3db"
        }
    ]
}